download-free-games.com 2014-03-31

# Privacy Policy - Download Free Games - Download Free Games

**Download Free Games (DFG) Privacy Policy**  
Updated November 3, 2009

DFG's Privacy Policy has been modeled after privacy expert eTrust (www.etrust.org) guidelines and on recommendations made public by the United States Federal Trade Commission (FTC - <http://www.ftc.gov/privacy/>) and the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA - <http://www.ftc.gov/privacy/privacyinitiatives/childrens.html>).

Download Free Games can be contacted via mail at:

Alpha Internet Consulting LLC  
ATTN: Download Free Games  
1212 N. Washington St. Suite 303  
Spokane, WA 99201

Questions about this privacy policy should be sent to [privacy@download-free-games.com](mailto:privacy@download-free-games.com)

**INFORMATION COLLECTION & USE**

**Personally Identifiable Information**

"Personally Identifiable Information" is information that we can use to identify you as an individual. Personally identifiable information includes your name, address, telephone number and any other information that is connected with you personally.

DFG does not collect personally identifiable information from you unless you give it to us through an order form or other form that asks you for it.

Please note that personally identifiable information gathered by us or by our third-party service providers can be disclosed to judicial or other government agencies subject to warrant, subpoenas or other governmental orders as required by law.

Any personally identifiable information posted by you in our user reviews or other service such as a forum may be displayed publicly if you give us permission to do so.

DFG does not intentionally collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13.

In the case DFG merged or was acquired by another company, all applicable information we have collected would be owned by the new company and subject to their privacy policies.  In the case of a bankruptcy, personally identifiable information would only be given to 3rd party companies as required by law.

To opt out of any information we have collected about you, please email us at [privacy@download-free-games.com](mailto:privacy@download-free-games.com)

**Registration**

DFG does not require registration to use any part of our site.

**Email**

In order to receive email correspondence from us in the form of newsletters or game alerts or similar programs, we require a valid email address that is confirmed through double opt in. Double opt-in protects your email address from abuse and is described in the following steps:

  1. You enter your email address in our online form and submit it
  2. Your email is sent to a third part email hosting service (i.e. Aweber) and they send a confirmation request to your email address.
  3. You must then open the confirmation request email and click a link to confirm your desire to be a part of our newsletter, game alerts, or similar programs.
  4. If you do not click the link in the confirmation email, you will not be added to our service.
  5. Instructions for unsubscribing are found in every email and can be done quickly and automatically without fear of further email sent to you other than a confirmation of unsubscribing.

Alpha Internet Consulting LLC (parent company of Download Free Games) is the sole owner of the information collected via email signup on our site.

**Orders**

If you purchase a product or service from us, our third party order processors request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date).

Our third party order processors use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we or they will use this information to contact you.

DFG partners with several third party order processors & content providers to bring our users the best selection possible. All orders are done securely through our third party processors. Here are links to their privacy policies:

  * BMT Micro - <https://vendors.bmtmicro.net/newdevelopers/privacystatement.html>
  * Trymedia Systems - <https://fe.trymedia.com/magnus/privacy_en_mn.html>
  * RegNow - <http://www.regnow.com/privacy.html>
  * Plimus - <http://www.plimus.com/privacy.shtml>
  * Jagex - <http://www.jagex.com/corporate/privacy.ws>
  * Big Fish Games - <http://www.bigfishgames.com/company/privacy.html>

DFG does not store any credit card information itself.

**Game Reviews**

We allow users to voluntarily submit reviews of games on our site. If you participate, we will request certain personally identifiable information from you. Participation in these reviews is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and email address), and demographic information (such as city, state, country).

We use this information to notify you if you have won a free game for submitting a review. We also post your name and where you live on our reviews if you have chosen to give us this information. We only use this information to promote the legitimacy of our reviews and not for any other purposes!

**Site Visitors**

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name and IP address, but not the e-mail address (where possible). Email addresses are collected if visitors double opt-in to our Game Club services. Email addresses are then only used by Download Free Games and not sold, rented, given, or shown to any other company for any use whatsoever. Our use of double opt-in email addresses is to notify visitors of new games added to the site, send tips, or any information related to Download Free Games' products.

**Cookies**

A "cookie" is a small piece of information sent by a web server to store on a web browser so it can later be read back from that browser.

Cookies are used on many download links to track referrals from this site. All full version purchases made from these downloads are then credited to Download Free Games from software developer partners on a revenue sharing basis. At this time, Download Free Games does not set any cookies itself. Cookies may also be used by our third party ad server companies Tribal Fusion and Google Adsense.

To opt out of BT Buckets geo targeting system, [click here](http://btbuckets.com/site/optout)

**Ad Servers**

With respect to Ad Servers: We are currently partnering with Google Adsense and Tribal Fusion to deliver ads.

Tribal Fusion Privacy Policy Information - <http://www.tribalfusion.com/TribalFusion/privacy.html>  
Google Adsense Privacy Policy Information - <http://www.google.com/privacy.html>

**Privacy Standards**

Download Free Games has partnered with eTrust to provide a professionally certified privacy policy. You may contact eTrust at:

<http://www.etrust.org/about/contact.html>

Any changes made to this privacy policy will appear publicly on our site at

http://www.download-free-games.com/privacy.htm/
